After so much hard work and moving in, let's
make my final year hostel room go from this
to this because if you think it
is still dirty then I can assure you that it is
much cleaner than before.  Hello which is I
nice.  My room may be messy but never
dirty.  So as soon as you enter the room, first
clean every surface with Rhino Colon.  After
testing it a little, I got so tired that I had to
take a break.  And then taken app.
Then next day I was ready to let my
friends help me arrange my room.  And
God blessed them.  Because now I was
not living with suitcases and carts but actually living
with my children.  But you want to talk about what's behind
the curtain.  Ok, bye.   Come back tomorrow.